<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Movie Catalogue</string>

    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="img_des">Photo Description</string>
    <string name="realese_date">Realese date</string>
    <string name="directors">Directors</string>
    <string name="russo">Anthony Russo, Joe Russo</string>
    <string name="april_25_2018">April 25, 2018</string>
    <string name="detail_photo">Detail Photo</string>
    <string name="des">Bohemian Rhapsody is a foot-stomping celebration of Queen, their music and their extraordinary lead singer Freddie Mercury. Freddie defied stereotypes and shattered convention to become one of the most beloved entertainers on the planet. The film traces the meteoric rise of the band through their iconic songs and revolutionary sound. They reach unparalleled success, but in an unexpected turn Freddie, surrounded by darker influences, shuns Queen in pursuit of his solo career. Having suffered greatly without the collaboration of Queen, Freddie manages to reunite with his bandmates just in time for Live Aid. While bravely facing a recent AIDS diagnosis, Freddie leads the band in one of the greatest performances in the history of rock music. Queen cements a legacy that continues to inspire outsiders, dreamers and music lovers to this day</string>
    <string name="overview">Overview</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="bahasa">Bahasa</string>
    <string name="movies">Movies</string>
    <string name="tv_series">TV Series</string>

    <string-array name="data_movie_photo">
        <item>@drawable/poster_aquaman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_a_star</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_avengerinfinity</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_birdbox</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bohemian</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bumblebee</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_creed</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_deadpool</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragonball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_glass</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hunterkiller</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_marrypopins</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_mortalengine</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_preman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_robinhood</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_spiderman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_thegirl</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_themule</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_venom</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_alita</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_cold_persuit</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_crimes</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_marry_queen</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_master_z</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_overlord</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_ralph</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_serenity</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_t34</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_got</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_breaking</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_arrow</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_doom_patrol</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon_ball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_fairytail</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_family_guy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_flash</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_gotham</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_grey_anatomy</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_movie_title">
        <item>Aquaman</item>
        <item>A Star Is Born</item>
        <item>Avenger Infinity War</item>
        <item>Bird Box</item>
        <item>Bohemian Rhapsody</item>
        <item>Bumble Bee</item>
        <item>Creed II</item>
        <item>Deadpool 2</item>
        <item>How To Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball Super: Broly</item>
        <item>Glass</item>
        <item>Hunter Killer</item>
        <item>Mary Poppins Returns</item>
        <item>Mortal Engines</item>
        <item>Preman Pensiun</item>
        <item>Robin Hood</item>
        <item>Spider-Man: Into The Spider Verse</item>
        <item>The Girl In The Spiders Web</item>
        <item>The Mule</item>
        <item>Venom</item>
        <item>Alita: Battle Angel</item>
        <item>Cold Pursuit</item>
        <item>Fantastic Beasts: The Crimes of Grindelwald</item>
        <item>Mary Queen of Scots</item>
        <item>Master Z: The Ip Man Legacy</item>
        <item>Overlord</item>
        <item>Ralph Breaks the Internet</item>
        <item>Serenity</item>
        <item>T-34</item>
        <item>Game of Thrones</item>
        <item>Breaking Bad</item>
        <item>Arrow</item>
        <item>Doom Patrol</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball</item>
        <item>Fairy Tail</item>
        <item>Family Guy</item>
        <item>The Flash</item>
        <item>Gotham</item>
        <item>Greys Anatomy</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_movie_directors">
        <item>James Wan</item>
        <item>Bradley Cooper</item>
        <item>Anthony Russo, Joe Russo</item>
        <item>Susanne Bier</item>
        <item>Bryan Singer</item>
        <item>Travis Knight</item>
        <item>Steven Caple Jr.</item>
        <item>David Leitch</item>
        <item>Dean DeBlois</item>
        <item>Tatsuya Nagamine</item>
        <item>M. Night Shymalan</item>
        <item>Donnovan Marsh</item>
        <item>Rob Marshall</item>
        <item>Christian Rivers</item>
        <item>Aris Nugraha</item>
        <item>Otto Bathurst</item>
        <item>Peter Ramsey, Bob Persichetti, Rodney Rothman</item>
        <item>Fede Alvarez</item>
        <item>CLint Eastwood</item>
        <item>Ruben Fleischer</item>
        <item>Robert Rodriguez</item>
        <item>Hans Petter Moland</item>
        <item>David Yates</item>
        <item>Josie Rourke</item>
        <item>Yuen Woo-ping</item>
        <item>Julius Avery</item>
        <item>Rich Moore, Phil Johnston</item>
        <item>Steven Knight</item>
        <item>Aleksei Sidorov</item>
        <item>George R. R. Martin, David Benioff, D. B. Weiss, Bryan Cogman, Vanessa Taylor, Jane Espenson, Dave Hill</item>
        <item>Vince Gilligan, Peter Gould, Thomas Schnauz, Moira Walley-Beckett, Sam Catlin, George Mastras</item>
        <item>Sarah Schechter, Wendy Mericle, Andrew Kreisberg, Marc Guggenheim, Greg Berlanti, Beth Schwartz</item>
        <item>Arnold Drake, Bob Haney, Jeremy Carver</item>
        <item>Akira Toriyama</item>
        <item>Hiro Mashima</item>
        <item>Seth MacFarlane</item>
        <item>J.P. Finn, Emily Silver, Brooke Roberts, Dermott Downs, Glen Winter</item>
        <item>Scott White, Rebecca Perry Cutter</item>
        <item>Ann Kindberg, Austin Guzman, Ellen Pompeo, Elisabeth R. Finch, Gabrielle G. Stanton, Harry Werksman, Jeff Rafner</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_movie_release">
        <item>December 21, 2018</item>
        <item>October 19, 2018</item>
        <item>April 26, 2019</item>
        <item>November 12, 2018</item>
        <item>October 27, 2018</item>
        <item>December 19, 2018</item>
        <item>November 28, 2018</item>
        <item>May 15, 2018</item>
        <item>January 23, 2019</item>
        <item>November 14, 2018</item>
        <item>January 16, 2019</item>
        <item>October 24, 2018</item>
        <item>December 20, 2018</item>
        <item>December 13, 2018</item>
        <item>January 17, 2019</item>
        <item>November 20, 2018</item>
        <item>December 12, 2018</item>
        <item>November 19, 2018</item>
        <item>March 17, 2019</item>
        <item>October 3, 2018</item>
        <item>February 5, 2019</item>
        <item>February 15, 2019</item>
        <item>November 14, 2018</item>
        <item>December 7, 2018</item>
        <item>December 29, 2018</item>
        <item>November 7, 2018</item>
        <item>November 23, 2018</item>
        <item>February 1, 2019</item>
        <item>December 27, 2018</item>
        <item>April 17, 2011 - May 19, 2019</item>
        <item>January 20, 2008 - April 11, 2013</item>
        <item>October 10, 2012 - Present</item>
        <item>February 15, 2019 - Present</item>
        <item>1984 en dash 1995</item>
        <item>October 12, 2009 - Present</item>
        <item>January 31, 1999 - Present</item>
        <item>October 7, 2014 - Present</item>
        <item>September 22, 2014 - Present</item>
        <item>March 27, 2005 - Present</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_movie_description">
        <item>Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, the city of Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom ruled by the power hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans to conquer the remaining oceanic people and then the surface world. Standing in his way is Aquaman, Orms half-human, half-Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne. With help from royal counselor Vulko, Aquaman must retrieve the legendary Trident of Atlan and embrace his destiny as protector of the deep.</item>
        <item>Seasoned musician Jackson Maine discovers and falls in love with struggling artist Ally. She has just about given up on her dream to make it big as a singer until Jackson coaxes her into the spotlight. But even as Allys career takes off, the personal side of their relationship is breaking down, as Jackson fights an ongoing battle with his own internal demons.</item>
        <item>Adrift in space with no food or water, Tony Stark sends a message to Pepper Potts as his oxygen supply starts to dwindle. Meanwhile, the remaining Avengers Thor, Black Widow, Captain America and Bruce Banner must figure out a way to bring back their vanquished allies for an epic showdown with Thanos the evil demigod who decimated the planet and the universe.</item>
        <item>When a mysterious force decimates the population, only one thing is certain if you see it, you die. The survivors must now avoid coming face to face with an entity that takes the form of their worst fears. Searching for hope and a new beginning, a woman and her children embark on a dangerous journey through the woods and down a river to find the one place that may offer sanctuary. To make it, theyll have to cover their eyes from the evil that chases them and complete the trip blindfolded.</item>
        <item>Bohemian Rhapsody is a foot-stomping celebration of Queen, their music and their extraordinary lead singer Freddie Mercury. Freddie defied stereotypes and shattered convention to become one of the most beloved entertainers on the planet. The film traces the meteoric rise of the band through their iconic songs and revolutionary sound. They reach unparalleled success, but in an unexpected turn Freddie, surrounded by darker influences, shuns Queen in pursuit of his solo career. Having suffered greatly without the collaboration of Queen, Freddie manages to reunite with his bandmates just in time for Live Aid. While bravely facing a recent AIDS diagnosis, Freddie leads the band in one of the greatest performances in the history of rock music. Queen cements a legacy that continues to inspire outsiders, dreamers and music lovers to this day</item>
        <item>On the run in the year of 1987, Bumblebee finds refuge in a junkyard in a small Californian beach town. Charlie, on the cusp of turning 18 and trying to find her place in the world, discovers Bumblebee, battle-scarred and broken.</item>
        <item>In 1985, Russian boxer Ivan Drago killed former U.S. champion Apollo Creed in a tragic match that stunned the world. Against the wishes of trainer Rocky Balboa, Apollos son Adonis Johnson accepts a challenge from Dragos son another dangerous fighter. Under guidance from Rocky, Adonis trains for the showdown of his life a date with destiny that soon becomes his obsession. Now, Johnson and Balboa must confront their shared legacy as the past comes back to haunt each man.</item>
        <item>Wade Wilson (Ryan Reynolds) is a former Special Forces operative who now works as a mercenary. His world comes crashing down when evil scientist Ajax (Ed Skrein) tortures, disfigures and transforms him into Deadpool. The rogue experiment leaves Deadpool with accelerated healing powers and a twisted sense of humor. With help from mutant allies Colossus and Negasonic Teenage Warhead (Brianna Hildebrand), Deadpool uses his new skills to hunt down the man who nearly destroyed his life.</item>
        <item>From DreamWorks Animation comes a surprising tale about growing up, finding the courage to face the unknown…and how nothing can ever train you to let go. What began as an unlikely friendship between an adolescent Viking and a fearsome Night Fury dragon has become an epic adventure spanning their lives. Welcome to the most astonishing chapter of one of the most beloved animated franchises in film history: How to Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World.</item>
        <item>A planet destroyed, a powerful race reduced to nothing. After the devastation of Planet Vegeta, three Saiyans were scattered among the stars, destined for different fates. While two found a home on Earth, the third was raised with a burning desire for vengeance and developed an unbelievable power. And the time for revenge has come. Destinies collide in a battle that will shake the universe to its very core! Goku is back to training hard so he can face the most powerful foes the universes have to offer, and Vegeta is keeping up right beside him. But when they suddenly find themselves against an unknown Saiyan, they discover a terrible, destructive force.</item>
        <item>M. Night Shyamalan brings together the narratives of two of his standout originals—2000’s Unbreakable, from Touchstone, and 2016’s Split, from Universal—in one explosive, all-new comic-book thriller: Glass. From Unbreakable, Bruce Willis returns as David Dunn as does Samuel L. Jackson as Elijah Price, known also by his pseudonym Mr. Glass. Joining from Split are James McAvoy, reprising his role as Kevin Wendell Crumb and the multiple identities who reside within, and Anya Taylor-Joy as Casey Cooke, the only captive to survive an encounter with The Beast. Following the conclusion of Split, Glass finds Dunn pursuing Crumb’s superhuman figure of The Beast in a series of escalating encounters, while the shadowy presence of Price emerges as an orchestrator who holds secrets critical to both men.</item>
        <item>American submarine Captain Joe Glass is on the hunt for a U.S. sub in distress in the Arctic Ocean. He soon learns that a secret Russian coup is in the offing, a conspiracy that threatens to dismantle the world order. With crew and country on the line, Glass must assemble an elite group of Navy SEALs to sneak through enemy waters, rescue the kidnapped Russian president and prevent World War III.</item>
        <item>Decades after her original visit, the magical nanny returns to help the Banks siblings and Michaels children through a difficult time in their lives.</item>
        <item>Hundreds of years after civilization was destroyed by a cataclysmic event, a mysterious young woman, Hester Shaw (Hera Hilmar), emerges as the only one who can stop London — now a giant, predator city on wheels from devouring everything in its path. Feral, and fiercely driven by the memory of her mother, Hester joins forces with Tom Natsworthy (Robert Sheehan), an outcast from London, along with Anna Fang (Jihae), a dangerous outlaw with a bounty on her head.</item>
        <item>After three years, a small business that has retired as a thug has experienced problems. Sales began to decline. Deception also faced a new problem when Safira, her only daughter, had grown up and started being visited by men. A bigger problem then arises, when there is a problem between his former subordinates.</item>
        <item>A war-hardened Crusader and his Moorish commander mount an audacious revolt against the corrupt English crown in a thrilling action-adventure packed with gritty battlefield exploits, mind-blowing fight choreography, and a timeless romance.</item>
        <item>Teen Miles Morales becomes Spider-Man of his reality, crossing his path with five counterparts from another dimensions to stop a threat for all realities.</item>
        <item>Fired from the National Security Agency, Frans Balder recruits hacker Lisbeth Salander to steal FireWall, a computer program that can access codes for nuclear weapons worldwide. The download soon draws attention from an NSA agent who traces the activity to Stockholm. Further problems arise when Russian thugs take Lisbeths laptop and kidnap a math whiz who can make FireWall work. Now, Lisbeth and an unlikely ally must race against time to save the boy and recover the codes to avert disaster.</item>
        <item>Broke, alone and facing foreclosure on his business, 90-year-old horticulturist Earl Stone takes a job as a drug courier for a Mexican cartel. His immediate success leads to easy money and a larger shipment that soon draws the attention of hard-charging DEA agent Colin Bates. When Earls past mistakes start to weigh heavily on his conscience, he must decide whether to right those wrongs before law enforcement and cartel thugs catch up to him.</item>
        <item>Journalist Eddie Brock is trying to take down Carlton Drake, the notorious and brilliant founder of the Life Foundation. While investigating one of Drakes experiments, Eddies body merges with the alien Venom leaving him with superhuman strength and power. Twisted, dark and fueled by rage, Venom tries to control the new and dangerous abilities that Eddie finds so intoxicating.</item>
        <item>Set several centuries in the future, the abandoned Alita is found in the scrapyard of Iron City by Ido, a compassionate cyber-doctor who takes the unconscious cyborg Alita to his clinic. When Alita awakens, she has no memory of who she is, nor does she have any recognition of the world she finds herself in. As Alita learns to navigate her new life and the treacherous streets of Iron City, Ido tries to shield her from her mysterious past.</item>
        <item>Nels Coxmans quiet life as a snowplow driver comes crashing down when his beloved son dies under mysterious circumstances. His search for the truth soon becomes a quest for revenge against a psychotic drug lord named Viking and his sleazy henchmen. Transformed from upstanding citizen to coldblooded vigilante, Coxman unwittingly sets off a chain of events that includes a kidnapping, a series of deadly misunderstandings and a turf war between Viking and a rival boss.</item>
        <item>The second installment of the "Fantastic Beasts" series featuring the adventures of Magizoologist Newt Scamander.</item>
        <item>Queen of France at 16 and widowed at 18, Mary Stuart defies pressure to remarry. Instead, she returns to her native Scotland to reclaim her rightful throne. However, Scotland and England fall under the rule of the compelling Elizabeth I. Each young Queen beholds her sister in fear and fascination. Rivals in power and in love, and female regents in a masculine world, the two must decide how to play the game of marriage versus independence.</item>
        <item>Defeated by Master Ip, martial arts expert Cheung Tin Chi tries to lead a normal life in Hong Kong until triad leaders draw him back into fighting.</item>
        <item>On the eve of D-Day, American paratroopers drop behind enemy lines to penetrate the walls of a fortified church and destroy a radio transmitter. As the soldiers approach their target, they soon begin to realize that theres more going on in the Nazi-occupied village than a simple military operation. Making their way to an underground lab, the outnumbered men stumble upon a sinister experiment that forces them into a vicious battle against an army of the undead.</item>
        <item>Video game bad guy Ralph and fellow misfit Vanellope von Schweetz must risk it all by traveling to the World Wide Web in search of a replacement part to save Vanellopes video game, Sugar Rush. In way over their heads, Ralph and Vanellope rely on the citizens of the internet the netizens to help navigate their way, including an entrepreneur named Yesss, who is the head algorithm and the heart and soul of trend-making site BuzzzTube.</item>
        <item>Baker Dill is a fishing boat captain who leads tours off of the tranquil enclave of Plymouth Island. His peaceful life is soon shattered when his ex-wife Karen tracks him down. Desperate for help, Karen begs Baker to save her and their young son from her abusive husband. She wants him to take the brute out for a fishing excursion then throw him overboard to the sharks. Thrust back into a life that he wanted to forget, Baker now finds himself struggling to choose between right and wrong.</item>
        <item>In 1944 a group of Russian soldiers escapes from German captivity in a half-destroyed tank.</item>
        <item>Seven noble families fight for control of the mythical land of Westeros. Friction between the houses leads to full-scale war. All while a very ancient evil awakens in the farthest north. Amidst the war, a neglected military order of misfits, the Nights Watch, is all that stands between the realms of men and icy horrors beyond.</item>
        <item>When Walter White, a New Mexico chemistry teacher, is diagnosed with Stage III cancer and given a prognosis of only two years left to live. He becomes filled with a sense of fearlessness and an unrelenting desire to secure his familys financial future at any cost as he enters the dangerous world of drugs and crime.</item>
        <item>When presumed-dead billionaire playboy Oliver Queen returns home to Starling City after five years stranded on a remote island in the Pacific, he hides the changes the experience had on him, while secretly seeking reconciliation with his ex, Laurel. By day he picks up where he left off, playing the carefree philanderer he used to be, but at night he dons the alter ego of Arrow and works to right the wrongs of his family and restore the city to its former glory. Complicating his mission is Laurels father, Detective Quentin Lance, who is determined to put the vigilante behind bars.</item>
        <item>Doom Patrol is a team of traumatized and downtrodden superheroes, each of whom has suffered a horrible accident that gave them superhuman abilities but also left them scarred and disfigured. The members of the team have found their purpose through The Chief and have come together to investigate some of the worlds weirdest phenomena. After The Chief mysteriously disappears, though, the reluctant heroes find themselves called to action by Cyborg, who comes to them with a mission that they cannot refuse. Doom Patrol part support group, part superhero team is a band of superpowered freaks fighting for a world that wants nothing to do with them.</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball, sometimes styled as Dragonball, is a Japanese media franchise created by Akira Toriyama in 1984. The initial manga, written and illustrated by Toriyama, was serialized in Weekly Shōnen Jump from 1984 to 1995, with the 519 individual chapters collected into 42 tankōbon volumes by its publisher Shueisha.</item>
        <item>Lucy Heartfilia joins the Fairy Tail wizards guild and partners with Natsu Dragneel.</item>
        <item>Sick, twisted and politically incorrect, the animated series features the adventures of the Griffin family. Endearingly ignorant Peter and his stay-at-home wife Lois reside in Quahog, R.I., and have three kids. Meg, the eldest child, is a social outcast, and teenage Chris is awkward and clueless when it comes to the opposite sex. The youngest, Stewie, is a genius baby bent on killing his mother and destroying the world. The talking dog, Brian, keeps Stewie in check while sipping martinis and sorting through his own life issues.</item>
        <item>At 11, Barry Allens life changed completely when his mother died in a freak accident and his innocent father was convicted of her murder. Orphaned Barry later becomes Detective Joe West. Now a crime-scene investigator, his dedication to learn the truth about his mothers death drives him to follow up on every new scientific advancement and urban legend. When his latest obsession - a particle accelerator heralded as a world-changing invention - causes an explosion, it creates a freak storm and Barry is struck by lightning. He awakes from a coma nine months later with the power of superspeed. When he learns that others who have gained powers use them for evil, he dedicates himself to protecting the innocent, while still trying to solve the older mystery.</item>
        <item>James Gordon is a rising detective in the dangerously corrupt Gotham City, where his late father was a successful district attorney. Brave, honest and determined to prove himself, Gordon must navigate the dirty politics of Gothams justice system as well as the rise of malevolent villains, including The Penguin, The Riddler and Catwoman. The series also chronicles the life of young Bruce Wayne, who becomes an orphan when his billionaire parents Thomas and Martha Wayne are murdered. Gordon becomes a friend to young Bruce as he finds his way toward becoming the iconic caped crusader.</item>
        <item>The medical drama series focuses on a group of young doctors at Seattle Grace Mercy West Hospital, who began their careers at the facility as interns. One of the young doctors and the shows namesake, Meredith Grey, is the daughter of a famous surgeon. Grey struggles to maintain relationships with her colleagues, particularly the hospitals one-time chief of surgery, Richard Webber, due to a pre-existing relationship between them - Webber and Merediths mother had a personal relationship when Meredith was young.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="category">
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
        <item>Series</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
